Guide to the Stanford Cardinal Broadcast Nework Videorecordings SC1123
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Cardinal Broadcast Nework videorecordings
1987-2004
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford Cardinal Broadcast Network
SC1123
10.5 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of videotape masters of SCBN programming, PSAs, and advertisements on a variety of topics.
Biographical/Historical note
The Stanford Cardinal Broadcasting Network (SCBN) is Stanford’s only student-run TV station. They broadcast to every residence and public television on campus. As a student and public access TV station, their goal is to provide the Stanford community with innovative, original, and targeted programming.
As a club, SCBN supports original shows and student filmmakers. SCBN also teaches a Production Workshop for those who are interested in TV Production and want to learn more. SCBN broadcasts programming, PSAs, and advertisements from the broader Bay Area community.
Videorecordings.; College students -- California -- Stanford.; Television broadcasting -- California.; Stanford Cardinal Broadcast Network
- Videorecordings
  - Election, 1998 Oct 31; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - SCBN News Open, 1998 Oct 30; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting, 1996 Nov 6; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Men's Tennis Spring Games, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Elections, 1999 Apr 15; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Candidates, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Presidential Debate, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Election Coverage, 1992; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting, 41008; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting, 1996 May 21; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Election Highlights, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - GSN #19, GSN #20, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - News, 1989 May 28; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Gender Presentation SVHS Footage, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Brainteaser (short film), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - The Stanford Scoop (Ep. 2), 2001 Apr 23; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Mock Pres. Debate, 1992 Apr 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Football (Year end video), 2004; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - The Stanford Scoop (Ep. 1), 2001 Apr 17; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Election Debate, 1998 Apr 9; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Decision 1997, 1997 Apr 16/17; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - SCBN Elections, 1998 Apr 16; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Election Night, 1999 Apr 15; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Debate, 2000; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - 1st Installment SCBN News, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - News, 2001 Apr 23; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - SCBN News, 2003 Feb 1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ASSU Election Telecast, 1993 Apr 15; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Live Edit ASSU Election, 1999 15 Apr; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - SCBN News, 1998 May 9; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - SCBN News, 2000 Jan 22; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 May 18; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 Apr 26; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 May 11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 Feb 27; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 Apr 19; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 2000 Feb 14; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 Feb 13; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 Feb 7; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 Jan 30; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1998 14 Nov; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1998 Nov 7; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1998 Oct 31; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1998 May 30; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1999 May 4; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1998 May 2; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1998 Apr 25; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1998 Apr 18; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN Promo Loop, 2000 Sept 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News Music Cuts, 1998 Oct-Nov; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News Raw B, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN ID Raw Cut, 1998 Mar 30; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News Chess, 1998 Apr 11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park - Maiden Voyage! Ep. 2-1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2-3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2-2 "Campy and Classic Horror Week", 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2-4, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2-5, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park, Apr 29 - 4 May; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park Raw, Apr 29 - 4 May; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2-6, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - SCBN News, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 1-1, 2001; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park, 2000 Jan 30; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 3-1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park, 12 Feb - 17 Feb; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park, 2001 Apr 16 - Apr 20; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park, Apr 16 - Apr 20; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park 3.2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Raw Footage Ep 3-2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park, 20 Feb - 25 Feb; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Invasion Stanford: 1991 A.D. Dub Master Ep. 3 & 4, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - The Stanford Scoop Ep. 6, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - The Stanford Scoop Ep. 5, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - The Stanford Scoop Ep. 3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2-2 Graphics, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Raw 3-1, 1988 Oct 28; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 3-2, 2000 Nov 14; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2-1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Raw Footage Ep. 2-4, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Raw Footage Ep. 2-3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park, Feb 20 - Feb 25; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Raw, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - SCBN News SF Summit for Women, 1999 Apr 26; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Call Backs, 2000 Jan 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Raw Ep. 2-3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 4, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 6, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - Trailer Park Ep. 5, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
  - The Waves, 1996 Jan 12; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Marines, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Democratic Convention Day 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Feast of Famine Ep. 104-107, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Straight No Chaser Ep. 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Straight No Chaser Ep. 2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - XTV Spring Demo, 1988 Mar 31; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - anti-Iraq Military Action Forum, 1998 Feb 19; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Wed. Night Live, 1989 Mar 8; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - People's Platform, 1996 Feb 26; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - ASSU Speakers Bureau, 2001 Jan 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Video Yearbook Kennedy Interview, 41053; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Love Links Ep. 1-3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Love Bites #2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - 2001 Stanford Film Festival (4 of 4), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - SCBN News Anchor Shots (Raw), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Wilbur + Warren Christopher, 1998 Apr 9; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Champagne and Strawberries, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - XTV News: The Farm Report, 1989 Apr 16; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - SSE Spot Master, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - SCBN News Inst. 1, 2002 Nov 21; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Cardinal Chaos, 1998; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Raw Footage: Campus Conference, 41054; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Teach In, 40931; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Free Speech TV, 1996 Apr 20-27; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - News Intro, 1999 Feb 1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Sexual Assault, 1997 March 11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - SCBN News Music, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - SCBN News, 1990 Oct 30; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Bhangra, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Bhangra, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Scenes of Stanford, 1995 Mar 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Feast or Famine, 1999 Jun 13; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - The Brit Awards, 1996; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Free Speech TV, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 4)
  - Dyeria Season 2, Ep. 2, 2003; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Dyeria Season 2, Ep. 1, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Dyeria Season 1, Ep. 5, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Dyeria Season 1, Ep. 4, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Dyeria Season 2, Ep. 3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - We Do Crime, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Town Hall Meeting, 1998 Feb; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Chuck Amuck, 1990 Feb 8; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - LCD Ep. 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - SVHS, 1998 May 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Final People's Court/Coffee Guy/South Bap, 1997 Apr 5; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Filipino Cultural Night, 1999 Apr 3; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Tree Stunt, 1997 Feb 28; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Eat My Videos (tape 3), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Dyeria Season 1, Ep. 3, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Dyeria Season 1, Ep. 1, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Dyeria Season 1, Ep. 1, 2002; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Haiti: Children in Crisis, 1994 June 28; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - The Draw, 1989 Apr 25-28; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TRT RE Final Cut, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - KZSU ft. The Donner Party, 40950; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Comm 114 Film Project, 1994-1995; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Campus Conference, 1990 Apr 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Bobsledder, 2000 May 23; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - The Normal Heart, 1987 Nov 11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Football Preview, 2000 May 31; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Campus Construction, 2000 May 31; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Pappa Bunko Susso, 1988 Oct 19; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Comm 117/118, Spring 1988; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - No Shame #3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - Men's Volleyball CSULB, 1990 Feb 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Dyeria Ep. 2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Lincoln Report Ep. 3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 6, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 5, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 4, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Voice #2, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Stanford Baseball/Tennis, 1990 July 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - The Stanford Scoop Ep. 4, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Women's Water Polo & Olympics, 1997 Mar 11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - SCBN Animation Test, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Debate B-Roll, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Cerebral Paisley, 1989; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Farm Feud Vol. 1,2 Ep 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - LCD Ep. 5, 1999 Apr 8; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - LCD Ep. 6, 1999 Apr 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - LCD Ep. 8, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - LCD Ep. 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - LCD Ep. 7, 1999 May 27; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - The Lincoln Report Ep. 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - LCD Ep. 3, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Voice Ep. 2, 1990; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 6)
  - Latin Awards, 1997; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Voice BLM Keynote, 40946; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Women's Basketball in Arizona, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Men's Volleyball (Stanford vs Pepperdine), 1991 Feb 8; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting, 1996 Nov 19; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Sketchy Folk Ep. 1 (DVD), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 1 to 3 (cassette tape), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - ASSU Election Promo, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Stanford vs Notre Dame, 1990 Oct 6; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Women's Volleyball Against OSU, 1989 Sept 29; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Road Cycling Championships, 1990 May 20; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Best of LCD Season 1, 1998-1999; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Snoopy 2Feature, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Honor Code Crisis: Trouble in Paradise, 1989 Dec 5; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Storm Drains PSA, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Fun Sound Mailman, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Stanford Youth Olympics 2000, 2000 May 31; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Stanford Baseball vs Georgia, 1990 June 8; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Baseball vs Cal, 1993 May 9; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Stanford vs UCSB @ UCLA, 1990 Apr 7; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Mela Master, 1996 May 24; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Sherifa Edoga Performance Piece, 1992 May 31; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - 2001 Stanford Film Festival (Part 3 of 4), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Stanford Men's Volleyball vs. Loyola, 1990 Feb 18; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - A-1 Grilling Ep. 4 to 6 (cassette tape), 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - H.M.S. Pinafore, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Ann Weber, 1997 May 17; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Meet the ASSU Senate Candidates, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Someday You'll Find Her, Charlie Brown, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - The Mayflower Voyage Cartoon, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Birth of Constitution Cartoon, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - D.J. Ep. 1 Edit, 1993 Apr 6; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Volleyball Intros/Promos, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Holla! Ep. 1, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - WRLP, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - A Charlie Brown Christmas, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Free Speech TV, 1997 Jan 25-Feb 1; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - That's Incredible!, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - KPIX Footage, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)
  - Free Speech TV, 1997 Dec 13-20; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 7)